Inventory of the Carter Family Papers 1667-1862
Earl Gregg Swem Library, College of William and Mary
- People Files, 1667-1862. (Folder 1-102)
  - Carter (Robert) of Nomini, born c. 1704, died 1731, 1712-1733., 5 items. (Folder 17)
    - Lease and Deed - Owsly (Thomas) to Robert Carter, 12-13 Aug 1729., 2 items. (Folder 17)
      Lease of a tract of land in Stafford County, 12 Aug 1729, and deed of sale covering the same tract of land, 13 Aug 1729.
    - Sale of land and receipt from John Savage to Robert Carter, 1730-1733., 2 items. (Folder 17)
      Savage (John) - Statement by John Warner concerning sale of 330 acres of land by John Savage to Robert Carter, 1730, and a cash receipt dated 1733.
    Subseries 18: Carter, (Robert "Councillor") of Nomini, 1728-1804
  - Carter, (Robert "Councillor") of Nomini, 1728-1804, 103 items. (Folder 18)
    - Letters, 1764-1803., 40 items. (Folder 18)
      - Daniel Dulany to [?], 22 Oct 1764., 1 item. (Folder 18)
      - A[nne] Ogle to Robert Carter, at Williamsburg, 15 Aug 1768., 1 item. (Folder 18)
      - J[ohn] Ridout, at Annapolis, to Robert Carter, 9 Oct 1768., 1 item. (Folder 18)
      - John Dixon, at William and Mary College, [Williamsburg], to Robert Carter, at Nomony [Nomini], [Westmoreland County], 3 July 1772., 1 item. (Folder 18)
      - Richard Parker to Robert Carter, at Nomony [Nomini] Hall, [Westmoreland County], 18 Sept 1772., 1 item. (Folder 18)
      - John Ridout, at Annapolis, to Robert Carter, Virginia, 22 May 1773., 1 item. (Folder 18)
      - Denton Jacques, at Annapolis, to Robert Carter, at Nomony [Nomini] Hall, Westmoreland [County], Virginia, 29 March 1774., 1 item. (Folder 18)
      - J[ohn] Ridout, at Annapolis, to Robert Carter, at Williamsburg, Virginia, 29 April 1774., 1 item. (Folder 18)
      - J[ohn] Ridout, at Whitehall, to Robert Carter, at Annapolis, 17 Dec 1775., 1 item. (Folder 18)
      - Richard Parker to John Tayloe, 18 Nov 1776., 1 item. (Folder 18)
      - John Turberville, at Hiccory Hill, [Westmoreland County], to Robert Carter, 28 Dec 1778., 1 item. (Folder 18)
      - William Hartshorn, at Alexandria, to Robert Carter, at Nomony [Nomini], 21 Aug 1780., 1 item. (Folder 18)
      - Catesby Jones, at Hiccory Hill, to Robert Carter, at Nomony [Nomini] Hall, 28 Jan 1785., 1 item. (Folder 18)
      - Eliza Steptoe, at Sandy Point, to Robert Carter, at Nomony [Nomini] Hall, 17 March 1785., 1 item. (Folder 18)
      - Thomas Beale, at Chestnut Hill, to Robert Carter, at Nomony [Nomini] Hall, 22 March 1785., 1 item. (Folder 18)
      - Travis Jones, on board the Mayflower, at Coles Point, [Westmoreland County], to Robert Carter, at Nomony [Nomini] Hall, 6 Dec 1785., 1 item. (Folder 18)
      - John Ballantine, at Ayrfield, to Robert Carter, at Nomony [Nomini] Hall, 13 June 1786., 1 item. (Folder 18)
      - Hudson Muse, Northumberland [County], to Robert Carter, at Nomony [Nomini] Hall, 10 July 1787., 1 item. (Folder 18)
      - Benjamin Lowndes, at Bladensburg, to Robert Carter, at Nomony [Nomini] Hall, 3 Sept 1787., 1 item. (Folder 18)
      - Benjamin and Francis Lowndes, at Bladensburg, to Robert Carter, at Nomony [Nomini] Hall, 3 Sept 1787., 1 item. (Folder 18)
      - Landon Carter, Jr., at Sabine Hall, [Richmond County], to Robert Carter, at Nomony [Nomini], 5 Aug 1788., 1 item. (Folder 18)
      - John Turberville, at Hiccory Hill, [Westmoreland County], to Robert Carter, at Nomony [Nomini] Hall, 4 Sept 1788., 1 item. (Folder 18)
      - William Newton Lane, at Carrville, to Robert Carter, at Nomony [Nomini] Hall, 9 Sept 1788., 1 item. (Folder 18)
      - Catesby Jones, at Cherry Hill, Northumberland County, to Robert Carter, at Nomony [Nomini] Hall, 13 Jan 1789., 1 item. (Folder 18)
      - Spencer Ball to Robert Carter, at Nomony [Nomini] Hall, 17 July 1789., 1 item. (Folder 18)
      - Richard Barnes Alexander, Prince William [County], to Robert Carter, at Nomony [Nomini], 26 March 1791., 1 item. (Folder 18)
      - Benjamin Grayson Orr & Co., at Hamilton, to Robert Carter, at Nomony [Nomini] Hall, 2 June 1792., 1 item. (Folder 18)
      - Spencer Ball, at Petapsco Creek, Virginia, to Robert Carter, at Baltimore, Maryland, 5 June 1793., 1 item. (Folder 18)
      - Robert Randolph, Fauquier [County], to Robert Carter, at Baltimore, 18 Aug 1797., 1 item. (Folder 18)
      - Mrs. [?] Purviance to Robert Carter, 19 Oct 1797., 1 item. (Folder 18)
      - Spencer Ball, Prince William County, to Robert Carter, at Baltimore, Maryland, 19 Oct 1798., 1 item. (Folder 18)
      - Samuel Johnston to Robert Carter, May 1800., 1 item. (Folder 18)
      - Ralph Wormeley, at Staunton, [Virginia], to Robert Carter, at Baltimore, 21 Aug 1800., 1 item. (Folder 18)
      - James Beaty, at Washington City, to Robert Carter, at Baltimore, 3 Sept 1800., 1 item. (Folder 18)
      - William McMechen, at Baltimore, to Robert Carter, [at Baltimore], 28 Nov 1800., 1 item. (Folder 18)
      - Spencer Ball, at Pohoke, to George Carter, at Oatlands, Loudoun County, 17 Nov 1801., 1 item. (Folder 18)
      - John Y. Chinn, Richmond [County], to Robert Carter, at Baltimore, 28 May 1802., 1 item. (Folder 18)
      - Robert Mitchell, at Grove Mount, to George Carter, at Oatlands, Loudoun [County], 28 May 1802., 1 item. (Folder 18)
      - Jo[seph] Jo[nes] Monroe, at Fonthill, to George Carter, at Nomini Hall, 14 Dec 1802., 1 item. (Folder 18)
      - James Carroll to Robert Carter, 9 June 1803., 1 item. (Folder 18)
    - Accounts of Robert "Councillor" Carter, 1734-1804., 60 items. (Folder 18)
    - Other Papers of Robert "Councillor" Carter, 1758-1788., 3 items. (Folder 18)
      - Appointment of Robert Carter as a member of His Majesty's Council in Virginia, 7 April 1758., 1 item.
      - Deed - William Carter to Robert Carter, 1761., 1 item.
        Quitclaim deed to a parcel of land on Palace Street, Williamsburg.
      - Court order commanding Robert Carter to turn over certain land in Loudoun County to Charles Carter, 18 March 1788., 1 item.
    Subseries 19: Carter, (Robert Wormeley) 1734-1797
  - Carter, (Robert Wormeley) 1734-1797; 1762-1795., 24 items. (Folder 19)
    - Letters, 1766-1788., 4 items. (Folder 19)
      - Robert Wormeley Carter to [?], 5 April 1766., 1 item. (Folder 19)
      - Robert Wormeley Carter, at Pallmouth, to Thomas Bryan Martin, at Greenway Court, Frederick [County], 6 June 1767., 1 item. (Folder 19)
      - Robert Wormeley Carter, at Sabine Hall, to Thomas Bryan Martin, at Greenway Court, [Frederick County], 20 June 1780., 1 item. (Folder 19)
      - Robert Wormeley Carter, at Sabine Hall, to John James Maund, at Winchester, 7 Dec 1788., 1 item. (Folder 19)
    - Accounts, 1762-1733., 18 items, including 9 diary books (typed by CWI). (Folder 19)
    - Other Papers, 1786-1795., 2 items. (Folder 19)
      See also: Morton, Louis, "Robert Wormeley Carter: Notes on the Life of a Virginia Planter," Journal of Southern History, vol. 12, pp. 345-365.
      - Deed - Charles Carter, trustee of Byrd (William) to Richard Parker and Robert Wormeley Carter, 1795., 1 item. (Folder 19)
        Deed to a lot in the city of Richmond.
      - Agreement of Richard Neale to sell to Robert Wormeley Carter, 260 acres of land, 1786., 1 item. (Folder 19)
    Subseries 20: Carter, (Robert W.) 1792-1861
  - Carter, (Robert W.) 1792-1861; 1803-1862, n.d. (Folder 20-101)
    - Letters, 1803-1861. (Folder 20-50)
      - Letters, 1803-1821., 44 items. (Folder 20)
        - Landon Carter to his son, Robert [W. Carter], 22 Feb 1803., 1 item. (Folder 20)
        - Landon Carter, at Sabine Hall, [Richmond County], to his son, Robert W. Carter, at Alexandria, 21 April 1806., 1 item. (Folder 20)
        - Landon Carter to his son, Robert Wormeley Carter, at Alexandria, 17 May 1806., 1 item. (Folder 20)
        - Landon Carter to his son, Robert W. Carter, at Alexandria, 10 March 1807., 1 item. (Folder 20)
        - Landon Carter, at Sabine Hall, [Richmond County], to his son, Robert W. Carter, at Alexandria, 20 March 1807., 1 item. (Folder 20)
        - Landon Carter to his son, Robert [W. Carter], 22 Feb 1808., 1 item. (Folder 20)
        - L[andon] Carter, at Salisbury, to Robert W. Carter, at Clermont, near Alexandria, 3 Aug 1809., 1 item. (Folder 20)
        - Landon Carter to his son, Robert W. Carter, at Clermont, near Alexandria, 6 Nov 1809., 1 item. (Folder 20)
        - L[andon] Carter, at Sabine Hall, [Richmond County], to his son, Robert W. Carter, at Clermont, near Alexandria, 1 April 1810., 1 item. (Folder 20)
        - Landon Carter to his son, Robert W. Carter, at Alexandria, 4 May 1810., 1 item. (Folder 20)
        - Landon Carter, at Sabine Hall, [Richmond County], to his son, Robert W. Carter, at Alexandria, 4 June 1810., 1 item. (Folder 20)
        - Landon Carter to his son, Robert W. Carter, 6 June 1810., 1 item. (Folder 20)
        - Walter J[ ones ], at Kensale, [Westmoreland County], to Robert Wormeley Carter, at Alexandria, 9 Nov 1812., 1 item. (Folder 20)
        - [?] Parker, at Springfield, to Robert W. Carter, at Sabine Hall, [Richmond County], 15 Feb 1814., 1 item. (Folder 20)
        - Landon Carter, at Alexandria, to his son, Major Robert W. Carter, at camp near Fredericksburg, 20 Sept 1814., 1 item. (Folder 20)
        - Landon Carter, at Clifton, to Major Robert W. Carter, at Sabine Hall, near Richmond Court House, 16 March 1816., 1 item. (Folder 20)
        - Landon Carter to his son, Major Robert W. Carter, at Alexandria, 17 Feb 1817., 1 item. (Folder 20)
        - Robert W. Carter to James Mercer, at Baltimore, 8 Dec 1817., 1 item. (Folder 20)
        - R. W. C[arter], at Fredericksburg, to R[ichard] M. Scott, at Alexandria, 25 April 1818., 1 item. [Copy]. (Folder 20)
        - Richard M. Scott, at Alexandria, to Robert W. Carter, at Sabine Hall, near Richmond County Court House, Virginia, 27 April 1818., 1 item. (Folder 20)
        - Landon Carter, at Wood Berry, to his son, Robert W. Carter, at Sabine Hall, Richmond County, 3 Sept 1818., 1 item. (Folder 20)
        - Landon Carter, at Clifton, to his son, Major Robert W. Carter, at Sabine Hall, [Richmond County], 13 Dec 1818., 1 item. (Folder 20)
        - Landon Carter, at Sabine Hall, [Richmond County], to John Browne Cutting, at Fredericksburg, Virginia, 18 Jan 1819., 1 item. [Copy]. (Folder 20)
        - Patrick Gibson, at Richmond, to Robert W. Carter, at Sabine Hall, Richmond County, Virginia, 23 June 1819., 1 item. (Folder 20)
        - Patrick Gibson, per John G. Robert, at Richmond, to Robert W. Carter, at Sabine Hall, Richmond County, Virginia, 27 Dec 1819., 1 item. (Folder 20)
        - John Daingerfield, at Tappahannock, to [Robert W. Carter], 21 March 1820., 1 item. (Folder 20)
          A memorandum by Robert W. Carter appears on the same sheet.
        - Robert W. Carter, at S[abine] Hall, [Richmond County], to the Governor of Virginia, 6 June 1820., 1 item. [Copy]. (Folder 20)
        - Robert W. Carter, at Sabine Hall, [Richmond County], to General A. Parker, Westmoreland County, 14 June 1820., 1 item. [Copy]. (Folder 20)
        - Landon Carter, at Washington College, to his brother, Robert W. Carter, at Sabine Hall, Richmond County, 20 Sept 1820., 1 item. (Folder 20)
        - Thomas M. Randolph, at Richmond, to Robert W. Carter, at Sabine Hall, Richmond County, 14 Oct 1820., 1 item. (Folder 20)
        - John Tayloe Lomax, at Fredericksburg,to Major Robert W. Carter, at Richmond Court House, 5 Dec 1820., 1 item. (Folder 20)
        - John Hooff, at Alexandria, to Robert W. Carter, at Sabine Hall, near Richmond Court House, Virginia, 8 Jan 1821., 1 item. (Folder 20)
        - John Hooff, at Alexandria, to Robert W. Carter, at Sabine Hall, near Richmond Court House, Virginia, 30 Jan 1821., 1 item. (Folder 20)
        - John Tayloe Lomax, at Fredericksburg, to Major Robert W. Carter, at Sabine Hall, Richmond County, 16 March 1821., 1 item. (Folder 20)
        - John Hooff, at Alexandria, to Robert W. Carter, at Fredericksburg, Virginia, 12 June 1821., 1 item. (Folder 20)
        - M. L. Carter, at Clifton, to Robert W. Carter, at Sabine Hall, [Richmond County], 22 June 1821., 1 item. (Folder 20)
        - B. 0. Tayloe, at Washington, to Major Robert W. Carter, at Sabine Hall, near Richmond Court House, Virginia, 5 July 1821., 1 item. (Folder 20)
        - M. L. Carter, at Fort Washington, to Robert W. Carter, at Sabine Hall, near Richmond Court House, Virginia, 9 Sept 1821., 1 item. (Folder 20)
        - John Hooff, at Alexandria, to Robert W. Carter, at Sabine Hall, near Richmond Court House, Virginia, 14 Sept 1821., 1 item. (Folder 20)
        - Mary L. Carter, at [The] Cottage, to Robert W. Carter, at Sabine Hall, Richmond County, Virginia, 10 Oct 1821., 1 item. (Folder 20)
        - John Tayloe Lomax, at Fredericksburg, to Major Robert W. Carter, at Sabine Hall, [Richmond County], 5 Nov 1821., 1 item. (Folder 20)
        - B. O. Tayloe, at Washington, to Major Robert W. Carter, at Sabine Hall, near Richmond Court House, Virginia, 5 Nov 1821., 1 item. (Folder 20)
      - Letters, 1822-1824., 33 items. (Folder 21)
        - B. O. Tayloe, at Washington, to Robert W. Carter, at Richmond, Virginia, 4 Jan 1822., 1 item. (Folder 21)
        - Charles Carter, at Corrottoman, [Lancaster County], to Robert W. Carter, at Sabine Hall, [Richmond County], 26 March 1822., 1 item. (Folder 21)
        - Charles Carter, at Corrottoman, [Lancaster County], to Robert W. Carter, at Sabine Hall, Richmond County, Virginia, 29 March 1822., 1 item. (Folder 21)
        - Charles Carter, at Corrottoman, [Lancaster County], to Robert W. Carter, at Sabine Hall, Richmond County, 9 April 1822., 1 item. (Folder 21)
        - Richard Henry Lee, at Leesburg, [Loudoun County], to Robert W. Carter, Richmond Court House, Richmond County, 13 April 1822., 1 item. (Folder 21)
        - Robert Page, at Janeville, to Robert W. Carter, at Fredericksburg, 6 May 1822., 1 item. (Folder 21)
        - Charles Carter to Robert W. Carter, at Sabine Hall, [Richmond County], 11 May 1822., 1 item. (Folder 21)
        - B. O. Tayloe, at Washington, to Major Robert W. Carter, at Sabine Hall, near Richmond Court House, Virginia, 20 May 1822., 1 item. (Folder 21)
        - St. Leger L. Carter, at Cleve, [King George County], to Robert Wormeley Carter, at Sabine Hall, [Richmond County], 27 June 1822., 1 item. (Folder 21)
        - R. H. Lee, at Leesburg, [Loudoun County], to Robert W. Carter, at Sabine Hall, Richmond County, Virginia, 27 June 1822., 1 item. (Folder 21)
        - Two letters written on the same page, from Robert W. Carter to St. Leger L. Carter, 3-28 July 1822., 1 item. Copy. (Folder 21)
          [Robert W. Carter], at S[abine] Hall, [Richmond County], to St. L[eger] L. Carter. 3 July 1822.
          [Robert W. Carter], at S[abine] Hall, [Richmond County], to St. L[eger] L. Carter. 28 July 1822.
        - Mary B. Carter, at Sabine Hall, [Richmond County], to Robert W. Carter, at Richmond, Virginia, 4 July 1822., 1 item. Incomplete. (Folder 21)
          Enclosure: [Charles Carter ?] to Mary B. Carter, at Sabine Hall, [Richmond County].
        - B. 0. Tayloe, at Washington, to Major Robert W. Carter, at Sabine Hall, near Richmond C[ourt] House, Virginia, 19 July 1822., 1 item. (Folder 21)
          Receipt for payment for ticket in Grand National Lottery appears on same sheet.
        - M. L. Carter, at Fredericksburg, to Major Robert W. Carter, at Sabine Hall, near Richmond County Court House, 20 Aug 1822., 1 item. (Folder 21)
        - Samuel Moore, at Baltimore, to Robert W. Carter, at Sabine Hall, Richmond Court House, Virginia, 27 Oct 1822., 1 item. (Folder 21)
        - J. Reynolds to Major Robert Carter, at Richmond, Virginia, 19 Dec 1822., 1 item. (Folder 21)
        - A. C. Tomlin, at Clifton, to Col. Robert W. Carter, at Sabine Hall, Richmond Court House, 11 April 1823., 1 item. (Folder 21)
        - Richard H. Henderson, at Leesburg, [Loudoun County], to Robert W. Carter, at Richmond Court House, Virginia, 13 April 1823., 1 item. (Folder 21)
        - M. L. C[arter], at Fredericksburg, to Robert W. Carter, at Sabine Hall, Richmond Court House, 21 May 1823., 1 item. (Folder 21)
        - P. Harrison to Robert W. Carter, at Sabine Hall, Richmond Court House, 30 July 1823., 1 item. (Folder 21)
        - [?], at Dumfries, to Col. Robert W. Carter, at Richmond, 8 Jan 1824., 1 item. [Mutilated]. (Folder 21)
        - Carter Mitchell to Col. Robert W. Carter, at Richmond, Virginia, 22 Jan 1824., 1 item. (Folder 21)
        - [?] to Col. Robert W. Carter, at Richmond, Virginia, Postmarked 12 Feb 1824., 1 item. [Mutilated]. (Folder 21)
        - An unidentified letter written in the House of Delegates, [Richmond], 20 Feb 1824., 1 item. [Mutilated]. (Folder 21)
        - R. Newman, at Brentsville, [Prince William County], to Robert W. Carter, at Sabine Hall, Richmond Court House, Virginia, 1 March 1824., 1 item. (Folder 21)
        - Tho. Brockenbrough, at Richmond, to R. W. Carter, at Fredericksburg, 11 March 1824., 1 item. (Folder 21)
        - D. G[?] Conway, at Stafford Court House, to Col. R. W. Carter, at Richmond City, 15 March 1824., 1 item. (Folder 21)
        - M. B. Carter, at Shuters Hill, to Robert W. Carter, at Warsaw, [Richmond County], Virginia, 18 March 1824., 1 item. (Folder 21)
        - [M. B. Carter], at Fredericksburg, to Robert Wormeley Carter, at Sabine Hall, Richmond County, Virginia, 5 April 1824., 1 item. (Folder 21)
        - St. Leger L. Carter, at Cleve, [King George County], to Col. Robert W. Carter, at Sabine Hall, Richmond County, 10 April 1824., 1 item. (Folder 21)
        - Lawrence Muse to Robert W. Carter, at Sabine Hall, [Richmond County], 26 July 1824., 1 item. (Folder 21)
        - St. Leger L. Carter, at Cleve, [King George County], to Col. Robert W. Carter, at Fredericksburg, 22 Aug 1824., 1 item. (Folder 21)
        - B. O. Tayloe, at Windsor, to Col. Robert W. Carter, at Sabine Hall, [Richmond County], 23 Oct 1824., 1 item. (Folder 21)
      - Letters, 1825-1827., 46 items. (Folder 22)
        - Mary L. Carter, at Fredericksburg, to Robert W. Carter, at Richmond City, 15 Jan 1825., 1 item. (Folder 22)
        - B. O. Tayloe, at Washington, to Col. Robert W. Carter, at Richmond, Virginia, 19 Jan 1825., 1 item. (Folder 22)
        - John Hooff to Robert W. Carter, at Richmond, Virginia,27 Jan 1825., 1 item. (Folder 22)
        - F. A. Carter, at Fredericksburg, to Col. Robert W. Carter, at Richmond, Virginia, Postmarked 30 Jan 1825., 1 item. (Folder 22)
        - John Hooff, at Alexandria, to R. W. Carter, 31 Jan 1825., 1 item. (Folder 22)
        - J. Marshall, Jr., at Mont Blanc, [Fauquier County], to Col. Robert W. Carter, at Sabine Hall, Richmond County, Virginia, 6 April 1825., 1 item. (Folder 22)
        - Robert W. Carter to John T. Lomax, at Fredericksburg, 17 April 1825., 1 item. (Folder 22)
        - John Lewis, at Lewis's Store, Spotsylvania County, Virginia, to Robert W. Carter, at Sabine Hall, Richmond Court House, Virginia, 20 May 1825., 1 item. (Folder 22)
        - Richard Henry Lee, at Leesburg, [Loudoun County], to Robert W. Carter, Richmond County, Virginia, 26 May 1825., 1 item. (Folder 22)
        - T. Turner, at Kinloch, [Fauquier County], to Col. Robert W. Carter, at Sabine Hall, Richmond Court House, Virginia, 27 May 1825., 1 item. (Folder 22)
        - Robert W. Carter, at Sabine Hall, [Richmond County], to John T. Lomax, 8 July 1825., 1 item. (Folder 22)
        - J. M. Selden, at Tree Hill, to Col. R. Carter, at Sabine Hall, Richmond County, 2 Sept 1825., 1 item. (Folder 22)
        - J. M. Selden, at Tree Hill, to Col. Robert Carter, at Sabine Hall, Richmond County, 10 Sept 1825., 1 item. (Folder 22)
        - Robert W. Carter to J. T. Lomax, at Fredericksburg, 29 Oct 1825., 1 item. (Folder 22)
        - William A. G. Dade, at Clover Hill, [Prince William County], to Col. Robert Carter, at Richmond, 1 Dec 1825., 1 item. (Folder 22)
        - William A. G. Dade, at Clover Hill, [Prince William County], to Col. Robert W. Carter, at Richmond, 24 Dec 1825., 1 item. (Folder 22)
        - William A. G. Dade, at Clover Hill, [Prince William County], to Col. Robert W. Carter, at Richmond, 11 Jan 1826., 1 item. (Folder 22)
        - W. Y. Sturman, at Westmoreland Court House, to Col. Robert W. Carter, at Richmond, 13 Jan 1826., 1 item. (Folder 22)
        - F[anny] A. C[arter], at Fredericksburg, to Col. Robert W. Carter, at Richmond, Virginia, 14 Jan 1826., 1 item. (Folder 22)
        - J[ohn] A[rmistead] Carter, at Sabine Hall, [Richmond County], to Col. Robert W. Carter, at Richmond, Virginia, 21 Jan 1826., 1 item. (Folder 22)
        - William A. G. Dade, at Clover Hill, [Prince William County], to Col. Robert W. Carter, at Richmond, 29 Jan 1826., 1 item. (Folder 22)
        - F[anny] A. C[arter], at Fredericksburg, to Col. Robert W. Carter, at Richmond, Virginia, 10 Feb 1826., 1 item. (Folder 22)
        - E. P. Cady, at Fredericksburg, to R. W. Carter, at Richmond, 2 March 1826., 1 item. (Folder 22)
        - J[ohn] A[rmistead] Carter, at University of to Col. Robert W. Carter, at Richmond Court House, Virginia, 3[?] March 1826., 1 item. (Folder 22)
        - J. Minor, at Fredericksburg, to Col. Robert W. Carter, at Sabine Hall, near Richmond Court House, 5 April 1826., 1 item. (Folder 22)
        - F[anny] A. C[arter], at Fredericksburg, to Col. R. W. Carter, at Sabine Hall, Richmond Court House, Virginia, 12 April 1826., 1 item. (Folder 22)
        - R[ichard] H[enry] Lee, at Leesburg, [Loundoun County], to Robert W. Carter, near Richmond Court House, Richmond County, Virginia, 8 May 1826., 1 item. (Folder 22)
        - Robley Dunglison, at University of Virginia, to Robert W. Carter, Richmond County, Virginia, 11 May 1826., 1 item. (Folder 22)
          Re: expulsion of J. A. Carter.
        - J[ohn] A[rmistead] Carter, at University [of Virginia], to Col. R. W. Carter, at Richmond Court House, Virginia, 15 May 1826., 1 item. (Folder 22)
        - F[anny] A. Carter, at Alexandria, to Col. R. W. Carter, at Fredericksburg, Virginia Forwarded to Richmond, 10 June 1826., 1 item. (Folder 22)
        - J. Minor, at Fredericksburg, to [R. W. Carter], 14 June 1826., 1 item. (Folder 22)
        - Charles Shirley Carter, at Cloverland, to Col. Robert W. Carter, at Sabine Hall, Richmond Court House, Virginia, 12 July 1826., 1 item. (Folder 22)
        - Charles Shirley Carter, at Cloverland, to Col. Robert W. Carter, at Sabine Hall, near Richmond Court House, Virginia, 5 Aug 1826., 1 item. (Folder 22)
        - Richard Henry Lee, at Leesburg, [Loundoun County], to Robert W. Carter, near Richmond Court House, Virginia, 16 Feb 1827., 1 item. (Folder 22)
        - Henry E. Watkins, at Richmond, to Robert W. Carter, Richmond County, 26 Feb 1827., 1 item. (Folder 22)
        - Richard Henry Lee, at Leesburg, [Loundoun County], to Robert W. Carter, at Richmond Court House, Richmond County, Virginia, 25 April 1827., 1 item. (Folder 22)
        - Richard Henry Lee, at Alexandria, to Robert W. Carter, near Richmond Court House, Richmond County, Virginia, 27 April 1827., 1 item. (Folder 22)
        - Samuel Pleasants, Henrico [County], to Robert W. Carter, at Sabine Hall, Richmond County, 28 April 1827., 1 item. (Folder 22)
        - John Dickinson, at Fredericksburg, to Col. Robert Carter, at Richmond Court House, 29 May 1827., 1 item. (Folder 22)
        - John Tayloe, at Washington, to Col. Robert W. Carter, at Sabine Hall, near Richmond Court House, Virginia, 14 July 1827., 1 item. (Folder 22)
        - Robert W. Carter to [Carter] Mitchell, 21 Aug 1827., 1 item. [Copy]. (Folder 22)
        - Carter Mitchell, at Wilna, to Col. Robert W. Carter, at Sabine Hall, [Richmond County], 26 Aug 1827., 1 item. (Folder 22)
        - H. R. Dulaney, at Washington, D. C., to Col. Robert W. Carter, at Richmond Court House, Virginia, 8 Oct 1827., 1 item. (Folder 22)